Daily Anti-Aging Supplement

* 
* Promo Code:
    
    NONE

Limited Time: Free Shipping On Continental USA Orders

PROMO CODE NONE

Your Privacy Rights
===================

Your Privacy Rights
-------------------

Last updated: December 16th, 2022

This policy applies to all visitors except those from the European Union. (For our European Union visitors, please [see here](https://www.leadingedgehealth.com/eu-privacy-rights).)

If you are a resident of California, please see below and also [see here](https://www.leadingedgehealth.com/california-privacy-rights).

Leading Edge Health Inc., a Canadian corporation ("LEH"), recognizes the importance of your privacy. Please take a moment to review how LEH collects and uses your information ("Privacy Policy").

Your Privacy Rights:

* LEH ACTS IN COMPLIANCE WITH THE CAN-SPAM ACT, THE CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT, THE CALIFORNIA "SHINE THE LIGHT" LAW, AND THE DIRECT MARKETING ASSOCIATION (DMA) PRIVACY PROMISE.
* We do NOT collect information about your general browsing behavior on the net.
* We do NOT know any of your internet search queries except for those that land you on our domains.
* We will NEVER spam you, and our third-party affiliate marketers are strictly forbidden to spam. By "spam," we mean the sending of bulk, unsolicited e-mail. If you receive spam containing an ad for one of our products, contact us at once. We will terminate the affiliate from our marketing program immediately.
* We are informed when someone clicks on ads on other sites, but the only information we have is the number of ad views. We do NOT know the identity of the site on which the ad was clicked, unless it is the immediate page before you land on our site.
* Besides our own website pages, the only page we will ever know you visited is the specific page from which you arrive (if applicable).
* We do NOT have discretionary access to your credit card information. Your credit card information is in a locked system, held by a certified Level 1, PCI-compliant third-party processor, for strict data security. If you make multiple purchases, their locked system will conduct the transactions. We do NOT have access to any part of the stored information, and we do NOT see the credit card numbers. There are strict obligations that govern credit card merchants' handling of personal data, and we cannot be held responsible for actions by this third party. We accept no liability for loss and/or damage that you may suffer as a result of this third party's acts and/or omissions. We advise you to print and retain a copy of each card transaction for future reference.
* Your order is shipped discreetly in a plain package with a shipping label that does NOT identify the contents.
* The purchasing, processing, and shipping of any product on the internet requires the buyer to provide certain data such as a name, shipping address, email address, and often a phone or fax number (we'll call that "Provided Information"). Such data are gathered via the website order page, mail or fax forms, or telephone order, and this information may be stored by LEH.
* The Provided Information is transmitted from your web browser to our order processing system using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). With this communication protocol, all Provided Information is encrypted prior to transmission over the Internet, and NOT sent as readable text. There is an inherent risk that any communication, whether by e-mail, fax, telephone, or post, however, can be intercepted by third-parties, and we cannot accept liability for that.
* Follow-up communications from LEH will ordinarily be limited to an order confirmation, customer service replies to questions you pose, newsletter mailings (from which you may naturally and easily opt-out at any time), occasional promotional offers (from which you may also naturally and easily opt-out at any time), the reset of your password if you so request, and perhaps a customer satisfaction survey. These may come by e-mail, SMS text, or phone. If you would like to opt out of newsletters, promotions, or surveys, not only can you unsubscribe at any time, but also can already opt out here or call us at Toll Free (in North America) [1-866-261-8661](tel:1-866-261-8661); international customers call (international calling code) [1-250-999-0414](tel:1-250-999-0414) (6am - 6pm PST). Unless you opt out [here](mailto:yourprivacyrights@leadingedgehealth.com) unsubscribe later, you shall be deemed to have given affirmative consent to receive such.
* Communications between you and LEH may be recorded.
* LEH markets a number of other brands, such as PrimeGENIX and GenuinePurity. If you receive an e-mail, SMS, or MMS sent specifically from PrimeGENIX, GenuinePurity, Leading Edge Health, or another associated brand, and you exercise your opt-out rights through the opt-out mechanism provided, this will not necessarily unsubscribe you from e-mail/SMS/MMS for the other brands. For instance, if you opt out of PrimeGENIX e-mails, you might still receive e-mails in the future stating that Leading Edge Health or GenuinePurity is the sender. To opt out of messages from any other brand like that, use the unsubscribe mechanism on the message of the particular brand/sender.
* We will not send you promotional SMS text messages unless you check the box where we ask permission to send them. Checking the box is an affirmative act, and by that act you are providing express, written consent to receiving promotional SMS texts. Providing your phone number is not a condition of purchase. You can opt out by replying "STOP" at any time. Message and data rates may apply. By law, we are not required to ask permission to send texts concerning actual purchases, such as order confirmations or delivery information.
* The Provided Information may be shared with select third-parties, who may notify you about products or services that they believe to be appropriate for you. If you wish to opt-out, you are welcome to use the contact information listed below to tell us.
* When non-personal information about you runs through servers and other mechanical devices to effectuate your transaction, we do NOT use it for any purpose other than completing the transaction and, potentially, for placing cookies so that ads might appear when you visit sites relevant to LEH products. We do NOT know the sites you are visiting when ads appear. (You can block cookies by changing settings on your computer.)
* Just as with any other company, Provided Information might have to be disclosed to a court of competent jurisdiction or a law enforcement agency if validly demanded, or may have to be disclosed in the course of a lawsuit, or supplied to a doctor or medical authority for your protection in the event of a health risk.
* Just as with any other company, our shipper will have access to that limited portion of your Provided Information necessary for sending you the product. The shipper is bound by a confidentiality agreement with us, and subject to applicable confidentiality statutes.
* In the event that our business is sold, Provided Information may be conveyed to the buyer, but the buyer will be obligated to honor this Privacy Policy.

How can I update my information?
--------------------------------

If your Provided Information changes, you may update or amend it by contacting us through the means provided below.

What happens when LEH changes its Privacy Policy?
-------------------------------------------------

We may update the Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the scope of our customer support, order processing, the law, or industry initiatives, among other reasons. If we make an update that materially changes a term set forth above, this will normally not apply to prior purchasers. If, for some, reason, it does, we will notify you using the e-mail address we have on file for you. Any changes made to the Privacy Policy will be effective upon the posting of the new Privacy Policy. The effective date of the Privacy Policy can be found at the top or bottom of this page, so if you come back to the site to make another purchase, please check to see whether the date has changed since your prior purchase, and if the date has changed, please make sure to read the policy again.

How can you contact LEH?
------------------------

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, or wish to exercise your rights, please e-mail us at

or

You can also call us toll free (in North America) at [1-866-261-8661](tel:1-866-261-8661) or (from outside North America) at [1-250-999-0414](https://www.genfx.com/emailpriv/1-250-999-0414) (6am – 6pm PST).

These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. This product is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.

\* Free Shipping to USA Applies Only to Lower 48 States (Excludes Hawaii, Alaska and Other Territories)

\* These trademarks, service marks, logos (including, without limitation, the individual names of products  
and retailers are the property of their respective owners and have not endorsed this product.

Leading Edge Health Inc. Leading Edge Health Ltd. All Rights Reserved.

Leading Edge Health Inc (300 - 1095 McKenzie Avenue Victoria, BC, V8P 2L5),

Leading Edge Health Ltd (171 Arch. Makariou III Ave, Vanezis Business Center, Office 401, 3027 Limassol, Cyprus)

LEM Processing LLC (6130 Elton Ave, Las Vegas, NV 89107)

**\*References:**

Arwert LI, Deijen JB and Drent ML. Effects of an oral mixture containing glycine, glutamine and niacin on memory, GH and IGF-1 secretion in middle-aged and elderly subjects. Nutr. Neurosci. 2003 Oct;6(5):269-75.

Biolo G, Tipton KD, Klein S and Wolfe RR. An abundant supply of amino acids enhances the metabolic effect of exercise on muscle protein. Am. J. Physiol. 1997 Jul;273(1 Pt 1):E122-9.

Chen LW, Wang YQ, Wei LC, Shi M and Chan YS. Chinese herbs and herbal extracts for neuroprotection of dopaminergic neurons and potential therapeutic treatment of Parkinson's disease. CNS Neurol. Disord. Drug Targets 2007 Aug;6(4):273-81

Chen MM, Yeh JK and Aloia JF. Histologic evidence: growth hormone completely prevents reduction in cortical bone gain and partially prevents cancellous osteopenia in the tibia of hypophysectomized rats. The Anatomical Record (1997) 249:163-72.

Chromiak JA and Antonio J. Use of amino acids as growth hormone-releasing agents by athletes. Nutritrion 2002 Jul-Aug;18(7-8):657-61.

Cohn JS, Kamili A, Wat E, Chung RW and Tandy S. Reduction in intestinal cholesterol absorption by various food components: mechanisms and implications. Atheroscler. Suppl. 2010 Jun;11(1):45-8.

Cuneo RC, Judd S, Wallace JD, Perry-Keen D, Burger H, Lim-Tio S, Strauss B, Stockigt J, Topliss D, Alford F, Hew L, Bode H, Conway A, Handelsman D, Dunn S, Boyages S, Cheung NW and Hurley D. The Australian multicenter trial of growth hormone (GH) treatment in GH-deficient adults. J. Clin. Endocrinol. Metab. 1998 83:107-16.

Dillon EL, Sheffield-Moore M, Paddon-Jones D, Gilkison C, Sanford AP, Casperson SL, Jiang J, Chinkes DL and Urban RJ. Amino acid supplementation increases lean body mass, basal muscle protein synthesis and insulin-like growth factor-1 expression in older women. J. Clin. Endocinol. Metab. 2009 May;94(5):1630-7.

Isidori A, Lo Monaco A and Cappa A. A study of growth hormone release in man after oral administration of amino acids. Curr. Med. Res.Opin. 1981;7(7):475-81.

Oono S, Kurimoto T, Nakazawa T, Miyoshi T, Okamoto N, Kashimoto R, Tagami Y, Ito Y and Mimura O. Pyroglutamic acid promotes survival of retinal gangion cells after optic nerve injury. Curr. Eye Res. 2009 Jul;34(7):598-605.

Rudman D, Feller AG, Cohn L, Shetty KR, Rudman IW and Draper MW. Effects of human growth hormone on body composition in elderly men. Horm. Res. 1991;36(Suppl 1):73-81.

Rudman D, Feller AG, Nagraj HS, Gergans GA, Lalitha PY, Goldberg AF, Schlenker RA, Cohn L, Rudman IW and Mattson DE. Effects of human growth hormone in men over 60 years old. N. Eng. J. Med. 1990 Jul5;323(1):1-6.

Sanclemente T, Marques-Lopes I, Puzo J and Garcia-Otin AL. Role of naturally-occuring plant sterols on intestinal cholesterol absorption and plasmatic levels. J. Physiol. Biochem. 2009 Mar;65(1):87-98.

Savine R and Sonksen PH. Is the somatopause an indication for growth hormone replacement? J. Endocrinol. Invest. 1999;22(5 Suppl):142-9.

Zajac A, Poprzecki S, Zebrowska A Chalimoniuk M and Langfort J. Arginine and ornithine supplementation increases growth hormone and insulin-like growth factor-1 serum levels after heavy-resistance training in strength-trained athletes. J. Strength Cond. Res. 2010 Apr;24(4):1082-90.
